okay it's 5:00 somewhere in gold at
least um and we will get started I
assume that people can
hear us uh from this room now and um my
name is Freddy Christensen I
am part of the AL gr forget organization
and together with me in this room I have
sorry uh I work with Fredy on AO for
GitHub uh you can see me sometimes
opening PS commending a CO requests and
we try to make it um as best as we can
for for you to
use in the room with us we also
have yes my name is Alexander I also
work with Maran Freddy uh as part of the
engineering system team at
Microsoft uh yeah so if you're checking
Theo repo maybe you'll see my name out
there too
very cool thanks
so what we'll do in this call is we will
very quickly go
through what's new since last time so
what what what's been checked into the
algo repository what's new functionality
in Alo for GitHub since our last call
that was uh the last Tuesday in
January um quite a few things are there
but nothing is shipped in the final
product yet everything that you'll see
here is in
preview um so we'll go through what's
new and then open up for discussion
after that um
now so the way that you can see what's
in preview and whatnot is actually this
one is a link to
aka.ms algo relase notes so I'll click
this one and it's going to take me to
the algo release notes and you can see
everything that in preview at any given
time in Alo for GitHub is everything
that is on top
of the first version shipped so version
6.3 is the latest version that has
shipped and everything that is on top of
that is right now in preview um or is
going to become preview very soon so
it's it's what's checked in right um now
as soon as we ship version 6.4 there'll
be a tag on top of this saying version
6.4 and you'll see that all of these
functionalities and features are part of
6.4 and then there'll be other things
coming in preview on top of that so
that's really the way to see whether
things have been um been deployed to
preview or not or in in a verion or it's
in preview going back to this one so
what's right now been shipped in preview
is uh GitHub app authentication the
ability to embed secrets in install apps
and install test apps um incremental
builds uh control workfl concurrency and
also optionally ability to push test
apps to online environments and also
some dication documentation I'll share
that with you there's a demo repo here
called AO office hours 20
25-2 and if we go to that one this is
containing the samples that I'm going to
show in this uh walk through
now GitHub app authentication uh is
really all about
hardening uh security for AO for GitHub
u in the beginning we had like personal
access tokens classic personal access
token and and very frequently they were
created for with no expiration date so
you can imagine that you create a
classic person access token God Access
with no expiration it impersonates the
user that creates the token has access
to all the repository and organizations
that the user have access to uh and it's
used to authenticate API over over basic
or or so the pro the reason why this is
a problem because this probably has
happened a lot people are creating these
tokens is that if they ever are exposed
if they ever like compromised rised uh
and and you don't figure out that
they're compromised then somebody else
have access to act like you in
everything you own on GitHub and then
that's obviously not very safe uh then
obviously you can create shorter
expiration dates but but there are other
means of doing that um GI up added find
gr personal access tokens which gave us
the ability to to limit uh which
repositories worked on they still
impersonate a user uh but they could be
scoped to one organization or select
repositories in that
organization the resource owner would
still be the person were like
impersonated and you could still create
those with no expiration date the U the
the actual token that you put in here is
the token that is going to be sent to
apis um to to do request and stuff like
that on GitHub now what we have now is
GitHub app authentication and that's
kind of like uh aad app authentication
Service to service in business Central
if you know what that is um where you
you define an app where you have an app
ID and a private key uh and based on on
this set of of values you can now create
or you can ask the app to give you an
access token that you then use to
authenticate to the API I over basic or
um it's still possible to do no
expiration date on this one because you
actually don't send the private key over
the wire to anything you only add you
only use this to create the access token
you're not using impersonation you're
using or it's going to be like a bot uh
when when you are when you are running
like update ELO system files with GitHub
app authentication and you can scope it
to one organization only and you have to
scope it to select repositories by
installing that app in these
repositories um there are some scenarios
that doesn't really work yet GitHub
packages is something that GitHub is
missing so you still need to create a
fine grain token for that but you can
create a fine grain token that only has
access to get up packages and use that
uh for that purpose and then a b that
was yeah opened this morning that create
release doesn't work uh I do have a fix
that I need to test whether
that's that's a fix for that but right
now it does not work in
Fred so the recommendation is to use
GitHub app authentication to to yeah
minimize the number of of access tokens
that you will be um sending over the
wire and can be compromised for evil
people other feature that is for
security purposes is the ability to
embed secrets in install apps or install
test test apps so um I don't know how
many people uses this but you have a
setting called install apps and a
setting called install test apps that is
uh the ability to to uh to give a series
of of URLs to apps that you'll download
and then install the problem is that you
might actually have a secret in settings
here right and and and we really don't
want that because uh this might pop up
in your logs this might pop up in um
when you create an issue on
Alo if we ask you to provide the lock
then then this lock might be there with
with your install apps and everything
direct is clear text and and so there's
a lot of reasons why we should not have
secrets in clear text in in in source
code settings or anything anywhere else
so what we've done in preview right now
is the ability to add like a dollar sign
and and some curly brackets and then
secret name and and then we will when
whenever we um use this URL we'll read
the secret and put that into uh this one
so there's an example here in the
repositories on how to use that so click
that and we'll see that here I have
actually install apps as an array and
it's just going to be like the secq
install apps and that could be be a URL
to a to a zip file with a number of of
of apps that I want to install in this
repositor um when we go into actual uh
build you will see that the install apps
is not the URL is not shown in the log
it's going to be shown which apps
actually are installed so the name of
the apps will be there but not the the
secret and the entire UR
back to this one um incremental builds
is something that we talked to a number
of Partners during Direction s last year
where we got a we had like
a a private round table with 10 Partners
discussing what what features they were
using and what feature they were needing
and one of the things was incremental
builds not really because the build time
takes a lot of time but mostly because
the publishing time takes a lot of time
so so so it's really a performance
enhancement that you can now build what
actually has been modified but the most
important thing is probably that you
don't publish apps that have just a new
version number but but hasn't really
been updated
um there's a setting called incremental
builds by default it is not enabled and
the reason for that is obviously that
the old version of algo did not have
this so we'll start out by by not
enabling this by default I don't know if
we'll ever do that or it's going to be
something that people can can do as an
organizational setting themselves but
right now uh you have to create a
setting called incremental builds and
then you can Define uh for three
different triggers whether you want to
run incremental bills or not it's on
push on pull request or on
schedule uh so if you're running a build
every night on schedule or every week on
a schedule then you'll have like a full
build every week if you set on schedule
to fals and then you can have
incremental Builds on push meaning that
it will take the artifacts from the last
known good build which would then would
be probably the schedule uh and and then
only build the apps that you define in
the
mode uh parameter which might be
modified apps or modified projects if
you set it to modifi projects it's going
to build all apps in that project if you
set to modifi apps only going to build
the apps that actually did change or the
apps that have a dependency on the apps
that have
changed um by default it's only enabled
on pull requests and that's because it
was already enabled on pull requests
earlier
um and uh yeah what it's the way that it
works is that all builds are actually
still complete so you will have all
artifacts but they'll have an old
version number so it's going to be
copied from from the last known good
build whenever we we we uh we do the
build so let's see an example of how
that
works uh in this one so this if we go
back to actions here and have a look
we'll see that this build
um is going
to have
three uh jobs here and this was done in
40 seconds this one in 50 seconds this
one in 16 minutes and this one and 12
minutes so these two apps the the DK and
the it one here was actually rebuilt the
other ones were not so if we scroll down
and have a look we'll see that it finds
out that the last known good build is
this one let's click at that and have a
look we'll see that this is a complete
build where where all the projects have
been have been built going back to the
the incremental build we'll then see
that the DK and the it1 was rebuilt if
we look at the artifacts down here we
will see that all artifacts are there
the W ones the common ones the it and
the DK but if we look inside the W1
apps and we download that one and click
here we'll see that this is actually
version
1.026 and if we download the DK main
apps that was was rebuilt in this one we
will see that that has version 1.0 to 28
uh the artifact the repo version number
is is the same on them all but the
actual apps have the version number of
when they were built and as such when
they try to publish those to an online
environment it will find out that these
apps have already been published and no
need to publish that beside the
incremental bills it's also recommended
to set up
[Music]
um workflow concurrency if you're
running with incremental builds and what
we can see here is that uh this this
build was the the full build the build
that doesn't have like incremental
builds that that's a full build and then
I did a modification here if we click
this
one
um this commit I did a modification to
the Italian version let's go back and
then shortly after a few seconds later I
did a modification here to the to the DK
one
so then when I did the modification
directly in the repo for the Danish
version it stopped the Italian build at
40 seconds and then restart a new build
for the Danish version and included the
changes from the Italian version
obviously and then rebuilt the apps that
were that were changed since the last
known good build so that's the new
Behavior figuring out what is the last
known good build build and changing uh
whatever has changed since then and the
ability to set up workflow
concurrency
um which I already talked about but what
the worklow concurrency is is a workflow
specific setting meaning it needs to be
uh in for a specific set of workflows
here in conditional settings or in a
workflow specific settings file that
also are there and the workflow
concurrency is described very well uh in
in settings or in GitHub where you'll
have the the ability to differentiate
whether you want to group on workflow or
on workflow and ref and whether you want
to cancel in progress or wait for it
afterwards
um this is the recommended if you're
running incremental
thingss another feature that was created
since last time is option the ability to
publish test apps to an online
environment uh the reason for this is
really the AI test toolkit and the the
the other test toolkits that are um we
are not at this point in time ready to
like run AI tests uh on like cicd or
automated so what we'll do instead is
we're going to prepare the online
environment for running these tests and
then you can navigate to them and and
start the tests at whatever time you
want uh the primary reason for not
running AI tests uh on every single
build is a matter of uh of cost because
it's not cheap to run these tests if
you're running uh them on every single
build so what you have is a setting uh
two settings in deploy two structure one
called include test apps in sandbox
environment and you set that to true it
will automatically deploy all your test
apps uh and their dependencies to the
sandbox environment when you are
deploying your apps uh you have the
ability to exclude some app iids where
you can just specify the goids of of
those and then it will not include these
apps if you have a dependency to test
test libraries which not which isn't
supported online
um we will not we will not try to deploy
that app uh I just talk to uh the team
that is working on the new version of
Testa libraries and and they do expect
in
um I don't know exactly it's probably
not going to be uh before April 1st but
it's probably going to be for October um
that they have a new version of the test
libraries which actually can be
installed online it's going to be
another app ID so you have to to change
your reference from test test libraries
to something else but then that app will
be an app source and and it won't have
the insecure functionality that were in
test test libraries that that yeah
blocks us from being able to to deploy
that to to online
environments last is a list of
deprication so we started uh actually in
January to deprecate some functionality
or change some functionality that
required some settings changes and what
we have have done is we've created this
Ms Al go deprecations you can click that
and see what is expected to change over
time uh changes to in effect after April
1st is the clean mode pre-processor
symbols instead of of using that you
will have to use conditional settings
with build modes clean and then
pre-processor symbols added
here if you're using that um and two
other that's going to be in effect uh
after October 1st is the setting called
Always build all projects uh instead of
that you should just set the onpo
request to false in incremental bills
and the setting where like the schedule
and the workflow name is is a like a
dynamic setting key name uh will be
changed to be workflow specific setting
uh called workflow
schedule um so some changes that will
need to be be done when when you
um it doesn't have to be ex as soon as
you update to the next version of Alo uh
but just before October 1st where will
stop supporting the old setting um so
you have
time with that I think everything is
there and we should uh yeah grab the
questions so I don't know if I can
actually open the questions here so we
can see the Q they pain in the meeting
as well can we do
that uh Johannes asks does Alo support
being used in private Vos yes definitely
uh we work we create a fork of Alo into
an
orc that only supports private repos and
deploys the template Repros from a fork
into private
Repros in the same private Fork of
course we need to keep
for
I I'm not entirely sure what you're
trying to do here so you created a fork
of
Alo and made that
private um
I
actually I think it should work but
um yeah maybe we should take that one
offline johanis so what you probably are
looking for is the functionality that is
in the in one of the PRS that has been
open for a while that we hope to get in
is the customization capabilities where
you can have an indirect template that
is really um a template that uses
Microsoft algo repository and then you
can have that as a private repository
and you can add customizations to that
and and change it to that um but yeah
create an issue or maybe we should like
set up a set up a call where we can go
through this in detail and and you can
show us what you're trying to do and and
and we can
um we can figure out what that
is
um there are a couple of questions
before that one that I tried to answer
while Freddy was
presenting
um the first one is uh just I think an
issue with the fact that GitHub abs are
currently not supported in version
6.1 you would need to update to
um is it 6.3 or preview preview preview
right now it's in preview right now and
will be available 6.4 6.4
yes
um the other question was about uh how
we find the last build last good build
and uh it is indeed Branch specific so
we
consider a build good build if it was
successful meaning our build jobs were
successful but and it run on the same
branch and there's a question any chance
to change the logic for release branches
release star to look for releases uh to
use a release as a baseline uh we
haven't thought about this
actually um so as a last no good build
yeah to use a release as a as a baseline
as a last long yes uh we could try but
it's
currently uh not we don't have any plans
to do it yeah
so so
the what what it does right now is if
you have a release BR it's going to use
the
release as
the previous version of that and it's
going to use like
um even as a time sensitive hot fix that
is not the release will be used as a as
a breaking change checking for breaking
changes but it wouldn't be used in an
incremental build right yeah so um I
mean could be a good idea I mean yeah
great suggestion cre an issue on on
GitHub and and might have a look to see
how hard it is I don't know you haven't
thought about that for in so if you
create a an issue a suggestion we'll
have a
look
um so there's a question on Telemetry
here since version 6.2 or 6.3
considerably less data is emitted via
Telemetry this the reason for this and
plans to increase the amount of data
again use this data
internally for creating dashboards to
see metrics such as build time
monitoring
inversions um to see the error messages
from a go One S most of the above and
more are unfortunately no longer
possible because the pow in transcripts
are no longer included in
theage that's we haven't we haven't
removed any Telemetry recently but I'm
just reading this for the Powershell
transcripts I'm not sure that was ever
something we locked in Al goemetry
sounds like something container
helper yeah cry and that's probably then
so you probably should be able to get
that um I think before it was like yeah
because the goemetry before went into EC
container H then everything was mer
together on that um but you might be
able to set up container hel elry to get
that still uh I don't
know but I think you should get the Eros
message and stuff like that right now or
are they not yeah I believe container
help with streaming quite a bit more
yeah but uh yeah maybe we can take an on
this and then we can we can see if
that's something we can enable like
having the old container helper
Telemetry as well yeah if you create an
issue on that uh floor and then we can
we can take a look at
that
yeah Emanuel uh never understood why we
have the actions like Alo actions run
pipeline pipeline
PS1 uh while CCD uses run pipelines on
BC container which we can override like
I struggle to do so for sign BC
container and we have actions like this
while CCD uses run Al pipeline from VC
contain not sure about the question here
but but I want to say that in the future
the the as go algo will stop using
container hel so over the next two to
three years algo will will create a a
different mechanism of building and we
um while we today can build through
container Helper and we can we can can
yeah utilize the overrides that we have
in container helper some of these things
will change
um and and yeah um
but not sure can can you elaborate on
whether this a question or it's a issue
that
you you're looking
into
um and you can maybe create another or
yeah elaborate on on that question here
okay
you have any other
questions so I
saw some of the people online I know
that lass already uses the incremental
builds maybe you
can share how things are working with
that
mostly related to not being so the issue
was mostly related to not being able to
override since it was since I thought
was using run pipeline from actions
Repro well right now you have override
functions and the way that they work let
me just share
the documentation go
aka.ms Alo
settings and then scroll to the very
end and there should be like container
helper settings that you can set I saw
that Florian also asked about partner
Telemetry connection string can this one
uh to to get your Telemetry sent from
container you might be able to use that
and these are the overrides that you can
you can override for functionality for
run a pipeline so if you place a file
called SBC container app PS1 in the algo
folder uh then
this this script will be run whenever
you um
whenever we get to the point of of
signing note that we recommend using uh
the new signing mechanisms where you
have the certificate in a in a keyboard
instead of uh the old mechanism trying
to do it inside the container which is
uh yeah somewhat harder trusted signing
on on aser can also be done in Alo
back
so other questions
yeah for people online please use this
time to share feedback ask questions if
you finding particular process too
difficult to understand this is your
time
I can ask so of the people online here
how many people are already using Alo if
you raise your hand if you're already
using
AO okay
then you can lower your hand again I'll
expect that the remaining people then
are people looking at whether or not to
use go
get there approximately
2,500
repositories can we can see in Telemetry
that are using a gr for
GitHub uh or that has been running
workflows and the majority of those are
on the latest vers
so we kind of these are the things that
we will be looking into from
Telemetry that that we can kind of see
if people are updating stuff like that
we cannot see who are updating or who
not but we can we can see statistics
if you don't have any questions then
let's know in the Q&A pain what is the
most Wanted feature what are what are
you really waiting for to like get into
Al go for GitHub that you would really
like us to focus on no promises given I
just want to he
using a custom built cicd solution in a
devop this is somewhere to see a demo of
full capability to motivate a change to
get don't think you'll have like
a somewhere I think the best solution is
probably to go to so the workshop it's
not like it doesn't cover everything but
it it covers to get started and how to
how to do things we've had quite a few
Partners going through the same Journey
H they're always surprised about how how
easy it is to use they go for GitHub
because they don't have to like maintain
workflows and write the animal typically
things that formally took
maybe hours or a day could now be just a
few settings here and there then and
things will be working um but again you
have unlimited flexibility if you're
writing everything and code yourself I
normally
compare uh cicd and devops
um in this area like how we were selling
nav in the old days where everybody had
their own version of nav basically with
code customized B app and stuff like
that and that now they're creating like
they're using a standard product with
some apps uh and and they are able to
update and stay current and all of these
things it's kind of the same thing here
if everybody using custom buil cicd
Solutions then everybody would have to
like enable page scripting enable AI
test toolkits and all of the things that
we'll be adding to algo that people can
can just adopt and use
everybody would have to to to create
those functionalities themselves with
like a lot of time spent and wasted for
that Florence say Most Wanted feature is
creation of runtime
packages
yeah had that before I'm surprised f it
just has
been it just has be has to be easy to
use
um yeah we hope it is
and obviously it's it's a different
learning TR to use Alo now instead
of instead of um writing code and and
all of these things you have to learn
about the settings but you'll have
you'll have Al go on on GitHub where you
can ask questions and there'll be us or
other people who can answer these
questions to to help you find the right
settings typically if you're looking for
some functionality that you think you
need to code uh yeah go look and see if
somebody else has been wanting that as
well and maybe there is a setting for
that um that you can
utilize also look in the release notes
that's just a a huge list of when things
are coming online they go
on the runtime packages let me talk
about that for just a few seconds
so um I was originally waiting for the
modern Dev team to or the developer
tools team to uh to create the fun
functionality in the AL compiler to
create onetime packages without the need
to have all dependencies in full apps
but could utilize symbols of
dependencies it seems like they're not
going to deliver that so it seems like
we have to create the runtime
packages um as we do now meaning that
really what we need to do is to create
some some workflows to automate this
functionality but you still have to have
full apps of your dependencies you
cannot create a onetime package of
something where you don't have the
dependencies to be able to publish to a
container and create the runtime
packages for that is that going to be a
problem for you Floren you can answer in
your in your own um issue
there with the growing of depositors
using AO will there be more comfort
feates to manage a lot of
repositories
um some of the things that we're looking
into there is the customization
capabilities or the the the indirect
templates really where you can create a
template like a template for your apps
of certain kind where you can have the
same uh a number of your repositories to
to utilize that as your template and
that is one of the things I know that
there's been a few people who created or
who working on
creating like powerbi dashboards to to
to look into these repos uh I'm I'm not
sure if those are going to
be utilizing Telemetry or they going to
be
utilizing um K have apis but
um let's yeah if you can tell us about
what comfort features you were thinking
about here is it like um
yeah and
let's he about
that yeah for Florence say for for the
runtime packages simple workflow is a
wrap off the convert BC apps to runtime
packages would be fine even though it
would take a lot of time um and yeah
that that is the current thinking that's
probably what we need to
do
so I think there was a question in the
chat yep
say after finally having a GitHub App
instead of a pit can we also have a
service connection to Ash subscription
via Federated like in Ado we'd like to
avoid having sequ as we do in Ash
credentials I don't think we have that
right now but that's definitely
something we we have
um we did create support for Federated
credentials but that still requires you
to have the ash credentials created
right um but yeah it's a good good idea
and it's definitely a
security topic that we'll have to to
look at to see if there's a better way
right I don't know if I think there's
something missing there from GitHub to
Ado that that they would need
to to make for us for for us to be able
to do these things but but we we'll be
investigating what functionality comes
online there um and based on this I'll
definitely have a look to see if there
is anything that
can can make it so that we can avoid
having
yes Cho both for the keyboard and for
like in general have to se
that L is asking if we're planning to
somehow expose runtime packages for
appsource apps uh we cannot do that um
so runtime packages is not a
guaranteed
[Music]
um it's not guaranteed you can you can
unpack the runtime packages you can find
find the the the code in there you
cannot find the AL code but you can find
the C code that's actually blog posts on
how to do that so it is it is not it's
upating the IP it's not really
protecting the IP hence if we were to
expose runtime packages for labsource
apps we might get a lawsuit from
Partners who didn't like that we've
talked about two different uh mechanisms
talked about the ability for partners to
opt in for to allow us to do that that
might be a solution so if you like in
your resource exposure policy in app
Json or wherever you would say it is
allowed for Microsoft to share runtime
packages for us uh not sure whether
we're going to ever get to that but for
algo users what we're thinking about is
the ability to have a workflow that runs
uh and then you can publish these
runtime packages a n get and then you
can share your Nate feed with Partners
uh so that they can trust your feed and
and utilize those that's kind of the
best
solution I did get a some feedback last
week from a partner saying that they
they were really sharing new get
packages with um with Partners on
a they they were not sharing the same
runtime packages to all Partners so they
had like a specific feed with like these
five apps is shared with this partner
and another feed for that so so they
were asking for the ability to to Define
multiple new get feeds for for for these
things and right now it go on support to
might be an easy fix to do I don't
know um yeah it's up to the isvs to
provide those feeds and we're trying to
make it easy for you to do that
Alberto says a great Improvement already
in the backlog is the possibility to
schedule the deployment to the
environment outside of working
time um yeah so we got this feedback at
the last office hour as well and I
shared a small uh small yaml file that
you can add that you where you can do
this you don't have a way to do this in
settings right now but you can take that
Dam file and and
added to your. GitHub
workflows uh folder and then you can set
up what time what branch and what
um what version you want to deploy so we
have partners that are deploying like
every Friday evening at
8:00 uh will be
deploying uh the current version meaning
the latest released version to to the
production environment and and and that
that seems to
P request BS I send
one yes are there any entry points to
implement own additional BLC build
checks for example the check for
checking the EX file is
complete um I mean I don't think
something Alo really has put than doing
no I think you have to write your own
workflow um we do that in the BC apps
repository we also have some additional
checks um I think something with the
clean tax and obsolete tax um Let me let
me share that workflow with you and then
maybe you can take some inspiration for
how we did that there but it's not
something EO supports I
believe you can create as many as you
want just by adding another P request
Handler right yeah workflow another
workflow Target
request yeah we don't really uh have
have examples for that but it's um just
a a GitHub work for this
10 more minutes to post your
questions comments or
feedback I didn't quite get the question
in the chat that was posted by
if you could elaborate a little bit if
you meant like the release
workflow the create release workflow you
have in G on Ino or something
else is there way to improve running
time of pipelines The Experience running
time to be about 20 minutes is that way
to doing caching
yeah so Peter and CHR so a few things
comes into mind here um a standard setup
will use a container to build U
and and that takes these like 15 20
minutes uh we are looking constantly on
ways to to do that better and we're
looking at I have a task of documenting
different ways of of of creating your
repository project structure to be able
to to build fast and then only use a
container when you actually have
to uh to run tests so you can add a
question in the Q&A to to tell us
whether you're you're using tests or not
if you're not using tests you can just
set
the um the setting called use compiler
folder to true and then do not publish
apps to true then you will cut your
build time down to like three or four
minutes U but then you're not able to
run test the idea is that if you have
multiple apps in a project or in a in a
GitHub repo you could build them all
using the Ed compiler folder and then
you could test them all in a different
project so you like very fast figure out
whether you have build failures and then
run the tests in other Cas we also have
Partners who are just building um in
their main repository and then running
test scheduled uh later so that they're
not like it it depends
we all our repositories run full build
and we're running full tests in every
single check in um
another way to optimize that might be to
uh to to run the tests in online
sandboxes which is not possible right
now but it's something we are we've been
working on as well
how many apps do you have in your repo
history like is it one app one repo
one custom
yeah probably nothing nothing you can do
now so you could could get it to fail
fast by by using compiler folder but it
will have to deploy and run the test
anyway so the total amount of time you
use for for setting up this would be the
same um but but we're we're aware of
that and and definitely looking to see
whether there are things we can do
better on
that
e e
five minutes
left there any
more topics we you'd like to make us
aware of
doesn't seem to be the
case then I think
we'll just stop a few minutes
early and say thanks to everybody for
joining us and we'll be back in a month
from now last Tuesday of March that's
going to be morning time at 800 a.m.
uh Central European
Time so it's for the the people in
Australia and New Zealand to
have a chance to actually participate as
well thanks a lot and have a good rest
of your day
thank you